<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Wyatt Pfeil</title>
    <link>https://wyattpfeil.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Wyatt Pfeil</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://wyattpfeil.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://wyattpfeil.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wyattpfeil.com/about/</guid>
      <description>Hey! I&amp;rsquo;m Wyatt. Throughout my life, I&amp;rsquo;ve developed a strong a passion for programming. Some fields that I&amp;rsquo;m currently interested in are game development, software creation, and artificial intelligence. On this site, you&amp;rsquo;ll find information about me along with some projects I&amp;rsquo;ve developed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://wyattpfeil.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wyattpfeil.com/contact/</guid>
      <description>Looking to contact me? Fill out the form below and I&amp;rsquo;ll get back to you as soon as possible.
 /* Style all select, textareas and input types except color, radio, checkbox */ input:not([type=color]):not([type=radio]):not([type=checkbox]), select, textarea { width: 100%; /* Full width */ padding: 12px; /* Some padding */ border: 1px solid #ccc; /* Gray border */ border-radius: 4px; /* Rounded borders */ box-sizing: border-box; /* Make sure that padding and width stays in place */ margin-top: 6px; /* Add a top margin */ margin-bottom: 16px; /* Bottom margin */ } /* Style textarea elements */ textarea { resize: vertical /* Allow the user to vertically resize the textarea (not horizontally) */ } /* increase the size of the select element to match others */ select { height: 4em; } /* add some space between the radio options*/ input[type=radio] { margin-left: 10px; margin-right: 5px; } /* add some space between the checkbox options*/ input[type=checkbox] { margin-right: 10px; } /* Style the submit button with a specific background color etc */ button[type=submit] { background-color: #0d0d0d; color: white; padding: 12px 20px; border: none; border-radius: 4px; width: 90%; height: 50px; cursor: pointer; font-weight: bold; margin-left: 5%; margin-right: 5%; } /* When moving the mouse over the submit button, add a darker color */ button[type=submit]:hover { background-color: #1091A9; } /* Add a background color and some padding around the form */ .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>iOS Apps</title>
      <link>https://wyattpfeil.com/ios-apps/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wyattpfeil.com/ios-apps/</guid>
      <description>Dot Flash Quickly tap all the dots as they get faster and faster. Each level is more challenging than the last. Build your hand/eye coordination. Try to beat your high score every time you play!
Have fun!
 Screenshots iPhone 
iPad 
   Learning Letters An app to teach children their letters and the sounds they make. A perfect app for young children ages 3-6 to help them get grasp of letters and their sounds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LearnToCode</title>
      <link>https://wyattpfeil.com/post/learntocode/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wyattpfeil.com/post/learntocode/</guid>
      <description>LearnToCode is a web app I developed in 2019 for the Pennsylvania Media and Design Competition. The aim of the project was to create a simple tool that helped new developers of all ages learn the fundementals of programming. LearnToCode can be accessed here</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TwoJs</title>
      <link>https://wyattpfeil.com/post/twojs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wyattpfeil.com/post/twojs/</guid>
      <description>I developed the TwoJS Javascript framework to provide developers a simple tool that can be used to create professional and responsive webapps. The framework uses HTML5 Canvas to draw shapes, buttons, images, and many other components to the page. The TwoJS designer can be accessed here and the Github repo can be found here</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>